Curriculum Vitae HONG QUY VO

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

## HONG QUY VO



- 3 Hamlet, Thuy Phu Village, Huong Thuy District, Thua Thien Hue Province, Viet Nam
- **+84** 975 44 97 12
- quy.vok37@gmail.com
- Skype quy.vok37@gmail.com

Sex Male | Date of birth 11/11/1995 | Nationality Vietnamese

## **OBJECTIVE**

The greatest desired in my life is that become embedded system engineer to develop advanced system in the world. I have already had experience in programming languages such as C, C++, Python, Arduino. In adition, I have done a lot of reseach projects in my laboratory and it help me develop my skills. It is an honor for me if I was allowed to be embedded system engineer in the your company.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Feb 2017 - Present

#### Research member

Smart Farm Project at Nara Institute of Science and Technology, Japan and Hue University of Sciences, Viet Nam

- Join to both research teams
- Go to the Nara Institute of Science and Technology, implementing the communication method for exchange data in the farm from February to August, 2017
- Do the webserver to storing and processing the data from farm object and user at home university

Internet of Things, Cloud Computing, Smart Farm

## Sep 2016 - Feb 2017

## Research member

Remote Control Robot Arm Project at Department of Electronics and Telecommunications, Hue University of Sciences, Viet Nam

- Write program in the TIVA C TM4C123G to control the robot arm
- Perform communication between robot arm with Android phone via Bluetooth

Robot Arm, TIVA C, Bluetooth

## Jan 2016 - May 2016

#### Team leader

Manufacture Equipment Capable of Detecting and Caring for Children Sleep at Department of Electronics and Telecommunications, Hue University of Sciences, Viet Nam

- Manage, schedule tasks for the team members
- Write program in Arduino to reading sound, accelerometer, gyro sensor to detect the waking up action of the children
- Interact with alarm device wirelessly via nrf24l01 module

Arduino, NRF24l01, Wearable device

Curriculum Vitae HONG QUY VO

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

## September 2013 - Present

#### Bachelor of Electronics and Telecommunications

Hue University of Sciences, Viet Nam

#### General

- English, Mathematics, Physics
- Informatics

## **Occupational**

- Circuit theory (Analog and Digital Circuits)
- Theory of automatic control (PID and Fuzzy controller)
- Computer architecture (Memory, ALU, Instruction Sets, Von Neumann, Harvard)
- Design the embedded system (Hardware and software for embedded system)
- VLSI design (Verilog language, FPGA, ASICs, RTL, Hardware simulation)

## PERSONAL SKILLS

## Mother tongue(s)

Vietnamese

## Other language(s)

## English

- Fluent in reading and listening
- Good communication skills at writing and speaking

#### Communication skills

- Proficient communication skill gained through my experience as member and leader in research project
- Good presentation skill gained through project presentation, conference presentation

# Organisational / managerial skills

- Good team-leading skills gained as previous team leader
- Good organisational skills gained through my experience as event establisher in university

## Job-related skills

- Programming skills (C/C++ for embedded systems, Python, Node JS)
- Digital hardware design (Verilog HDL, modelSim, Altera FPGA)

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

## **Publications**

An IoT Monitoring Prototype System for Smart Farm Using Zigbee and Raspberry Pi, IEICE RCS conference, Hokkaido, Japan, July, 2017

Study and Design of Remote Controlled Robotic Arm Via Bluetooth Technology, Hue University Scientific Magazine, February, 2017

## Honours and awards

Consolation prize: Hue Youth Science and Technology Innovation Competition in May, 2016

JASSO (Japan Student Services Organization) scholarship from Feb 2017 to August 2017

## References

Ho Duc Tam Linh

Counsellor: Electronics and Telecommunications Department, Hue University of Sciences

Email: <a href="mailto:hodutali@gmail.com">hodutali@gmail.com</a> Mobile: +84 981 166 226